If you had to give advice to
yourself, at the beginning of this experience,
what would you say?   Good thing I did
n't know what was waiting for me
.  [laughter]
He's a guy who's just starting out and who ca
n't give up, who has to study,
who also has to have the humility to
start doing something that maybe he didn't
expect to be what he
wanted at the beginning, but that over time,
if you apply yourself, things work out.  Try
to do things without talking about them too much.
What talents are you looking for in your company today?
Which figures do you
need most?  We need
new skills, especially regarding
electrification, software, and this is what
engineers are concerned with.  We are talking
more about the capacity of internal combustion engine vehicles than we thought a few years
ago
, so
this still remains very important.
More than I ever imagined.
Yes. M.